

JACKSON KUFFEL

Director | Writer | Marketer

PROFILE

Jackson Kuffel is a content creator, filmmaker, and student with eight years of dedicated experience in media production. Beginning as a pastime with friends while living in Connecticut, Jackson developed a steady passion for storytelling through visual mediums and incorporated his skills into the various churches at which his dad was pastoring. Upon relocating to Buffalo, Jackson enrolled in Buffalo State College with a double major in Business and Film as a concentrated first step towards developing MuseHub, a video marketing business focused on merging storytelling with advertising.

L

(716) 713-1489



jaxcalebkuffel@gmail.com



www.jacksonkmedia.com

SOCIAL MEDIA

Facebook

facebook.com/jaxcalebkuffel

Instagram

instagram.com/json_kuffel

EXPERIENCE

2022 - Present Co-Owner, Director

MuseHub, LLC

Founder of MuseHub, LLC and specialist in video production and storytelling, with primary concentration in client relations, script writing, and direction of productions.

2019 - Present Olde World Cheese Team Member

Wegmans

Department associate knowledgeable in a wide variety of cheeses and their ideal parings. Focused attention to customer service, task management, and inter-team cooperation, specifically during evening hours without managerial supervision.

2018 - Present Head Media Specialist

Amherst Baptist Church

Overseer and head of content creation in ministry promotions, event recaps, and testimonial videos. Camera operator and graphic designer for weekly service livestreaming.

EDUCATION



2020 - Present Bachelor of Television and Film Arts

Buffalo State College

The Television and Film Arts program is a highly selective program specializing in preparing students for roles in the entertainment industry through practical exercises in directing, screenwriting, and production.

2020 - Present Bachelor of Business Administration

Buffalo State College

With a selected concentration in marketing, the Business Administration program focuses on the development of leadership and communication skills and gaining of proficiency in economics, management, and advertising.

2016 Acting Student

Frank Rossi Studio

Taught by the casting director of *Marshall* and *Cabrini*, Frank Rossi offers individual and group instruction in the Meisner and Adler methods of acting with a focus on preparing students for roles in entertainment and advertising.

SKILLS



Professional

Premiere Photoshop Cinematography Directing Writing

Awards

2018 – Present
Phi Theta Kappa Member
2020 – Present
Alpha Lambda Delta Member
2021 – Present

National Society of Leadership & Success Member

REFERENCE



Arthur Baker

Owner, West Coast Forensic
P. (813) 838-3842

E. acb@westcoastforensic.com

Tim Endersby

Networking and Systems Administrator, Integron
P. (860) 307-3478
E. endersbyt@gmail.com